Guide to the Henry Taube Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2005-081
  - NIH lecture – Electron Transfer in Chem. Reactions [transparencies] (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Search for a Fuel Cell, etc. [transparencies] (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ACS Awards in inorganic chemistry [photocopies of transparencies] (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii [did not go] April 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Poster: Great Science under One Country, Two Systems – public lectures by Nobel Laureates, Hong Kong 1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Travels, Taube (correspondence), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence re lectures, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Visitors to Stanford, correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Lectures, correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Intramolecular transfer [film slides] (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - I- + Peroxides, correspondence re article, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - El. Transfer #2 Catalyt. [transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Electron Transfer – Undergrad. Invited lecture [transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Discovery, etc. – University of Virginia, Auburn University [transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Quadri-Science, correspondence, 1964-66 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mixed Valence Molecules research correspondence 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences election, correspondence, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NMR Seminar, lecture notes, 1957-58 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Talks – cooperative research [film slides] (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Armor et. al., Reduction of N20 – correspondence, illustrations, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Slides [text for transparencies] – Brooklyn Poly 1967 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous lecture slides [text for transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Illustrations and slides [text for] (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Industrial Affiliates – Theory e.t. [transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - C10-4 [transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Droege [transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Affiliates [transparencies] 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Slides [text for] (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Electronic Coupling Mechanisms in Mixed Valence Molecules, NYAS [text for transparencies] (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Slides [text for transparencies] March/April 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Slides – ACS meeting New York [text for transparencies] August 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Slides – Wayne State, Detroit [text for transparencies] May 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Slides – Nuclear Medicine, Detroit [text for transparencies] June 24, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Slides [text for transparencies] miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sabbatical – England [text for transparencies] 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, research proposal and correspondence, 1962-68 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Research reports, 1953-68 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Naval Research reports (Oxygen Atom Transfer processes) 1949-57 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - W. C. Bray's syllabus [photocopied] for chemistry 120 (U.C.) 1941 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Pauling Institute Symposium opening remarks 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hercules Research Center, correspondence, 1968-75 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - U.S. / Brazil program in chemistry, 1972-75 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - O3 + H2O2 + Br – article correspondence, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NIH - Ruthenium compounds for anti-tumor screening, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Pure Chemistry Award, ACS, correspondence and papers, 1960-81 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Awards – Garvan Award, ACS, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Senior U.S. Scientist Humboldt Award, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - California Scientist of the Year Award, 1972-75 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Wheland Medal Award Committee, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Awards – Nichols Award, ACS, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - American Chemical Society, Distinguished Foreign Scientist, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript, unlabeled article (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Chemical Physics, Journal of – correspondence 1959-65 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - CIO2 Exchange #13 [correspondence, notes], 1949 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Direct and Sensitized Photochemically Induced Reaction of Chlorine and Oxalic Acid" – correspondence re publication [#9] of article, 1946-47 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Phthalocyanine #26 [correspondence], 1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cr+++ aq, Co+++ aq exchanges #24 [typescript] 1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - O3 + C1- #15 [correspondence] 1949 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - New Chemistry of Hexacyano Ion Pairs [transparencies] (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dodel, Peter, correspondence with and about, 1963-65 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Substitution, notes for lecture (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Notes [properties of systems?] (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - ACS Award for Distinguished Service in the Advancement of Inorganic Chemistry, correspondence 1967-79 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Awards – Peter Debye Award in Physical Chemistry, correspondence 1962-70 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Awards – Yost – ACS (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - ACS Award for Distinguished Service in the Advancement of Inorganic Chemistry: congratulatory correspondence on Taube's wining of award, 1966-67 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Group Theory Applications – article and notes (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Solid State – notes for lecture (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nitrosyls & N2O4 – notes for lecture (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Biradicals – notes (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Intramolecular Electron Transfer: Baker Laurente lecture, typescript and notes (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - India and London, correspondence and photographs, 1969-71 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Hungarian Chemical Society Symposium on Coordination Chemistry and 8th ICCC, Vienna – correspondence and abstract 1964 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Tihany (Hungary) Symposium [on Coordination Chemistry] – correspondence and papers 1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Nitrogen-Bound and Carbon-Bound Xanthine Complexes of Ruthenium Ammines – correspondence re publication, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Acetate Complexes of Dirhodium and Diruthenium: Aquation and Redox – correspondence re publication, 1974-75 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Ruthenium Promoted Oxidation of Amines – correspondence re publication, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - the Mixed Valence State Based on μ-cyanogen Bis – correspondence re publication, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - N to O Isomerization of the Penta-ammineruthenium (III) glycine ion – correspondence re publication, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Zwickel, et. al. – correspondence re publication of their paper 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Chemical Research, Accounts of – correspondence 1968-70 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Australia [conferences] – correspondence 1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - The Infrared Spectrum and Structure of Matrix-Isolated Sulfur Tetroxide – correspondence re publication with some figures and charts 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Barrett, Martha, et. al. – correspondence re publication of article and illustrations, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Armor et. al. – correspondence re publication of article and illustrations, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Schmidt et. al.. – correspondence re publication of article, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bowen et. al.. – correspondence re publication of article and illustrations, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Pentaammineruthenium-Guanine Complexes – correspondence re publication of article, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Scott, Taube: Trifuoromethyl… – correspondence re publication of article, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - White, Taube: Reduction of Cobalt(III)… – correspondence re publication of article, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gauder [Reduction of complexes…] – correspondence re publication of article, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Armor [Equilibria and Rates…] – correspondence re publication of article, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Synthesis and Properties of Osmium(II) and Osmium(III) Ammine Complexes of Aromatic Nitrogen Heterocyclics – correspondence re publication of article with illustrations, 1974-75 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Adventures in the Land of Os – correspondence re publication of article, 1975-77 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Binding of a Tetraammine Ruthenium Complex to Imidazole and Purine Derivatives under equilibrium conditions – correspondence re publication of article, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - μ-Pyrazine Polynuclear Mixed Valence Species Based on trans Ruthenium Tetraammines – correspondence re publication of article and illustrations, 1977-78 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Chemistry of trans-Aquonitrosyl-tetraamminetechnetium I and related studies – correspondence re publication of article, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - The Exchange between Solvated Cations and Solvent. II. – figures for article, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Some Reactions of Ground-State (3P) and Electronically Excited (1D) Sulfur Atoms – correspondence re publication of article and illustrations, 1969-70 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - White, et. al., Characterization of Pentaaquomonoamminecobalt(III) – correspondence re publication of article, 1969-70 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Olson and Taube, The Chromium(II) Reduction of Maleato-pentaamminecobalt(III) – correspondence re publication of article and illustrations, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Diaz and Taube, Self-Exchange of Chromium(II)… – correspondence re publication of article, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Observations on Atom Transfer Reaction – paper presented at Wayne State University, June 1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Nucleophilic Attack on Cyanoformate induced by Coordination to Ruthenium Ammines – correspondence re publication of article, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - New Mo(II) and Mo(III) Species – correspondence re publication of article, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Sundberg, Nitrogen-Bound and Carbon-Bound… – correspondence re publication of article, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - New Complexes of Dirhodium(II) – correspondence re publication of article, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Crystal Structure of a Compound Featuring Caffeine Bound at C8 to Ruthenium(III) – correspondence re publication of article and computer printout of results, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Rutheniumammine Complexes of Hydrogen Sulfide and Related Sulfur Ligands – typescript, figures, and correspondence re publication of article, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - The Reduction of Pyrazine Oxide, Free and Coordinated to Ru(II) – correspondence re publication of article with some notes and figures, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Effects of Sulfur Dioxide, Bisulfite and Sulfite Ions as Auxiliary Ligands on the Reactivity of Ammineruthenium(II)-L Bonds – correspondence re publication of article, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Mixed Valence Complexes of Ruthenium Ammines with 4, 4' bipyridine as Bridging Ligand – correspondence re publication of article, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - The Mild Selective Conversion of Nitriles to Amides – correspondence re publication of article, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Intramolecular Electron Transfer Mediated of 4-4'-bipyridine and related bridging groups – correspondence re publication of article with notes, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Synthesis of (Trifluoromethanesulfonato)pentaammineosmium(III) Osmium(III) Pentaamine Complexes – correspondence re publication of article, 1982-83 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mixed Valence Pyrazine-Bridged Binuclear Complexes – text and correspondence re publication of article, 1982-83 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Rates of Substitution in cis- and trans- Ruthenium(II)aquotetraammines – correspondence re publication of article, 1975-76 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Electronic Interactions in Mixed-Valence Molecules as Mediated by Organic Bridging Groups – correspondence re publication of article with notes, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - The Interaction of HCN with (Ru(NH3)5H2O)2+ – correspondence re publication of article, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Studies on Oxidation-Reduction Reactions of Ruthenium Ammines – correspondence re publication of article, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - On the Reactivity of Imidazoliumrutheniuamammine Complexes – text, figures, and correspondence re publication of article, 1980-82 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Reactions of Matrix-Isolated SO2 with O(3P) and with O(1D) – text and correspondence re publication of article, 1975-76 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Absorption & MCD Spectral Studies of the Decaammine-mu-(Dinitrogen-N,N1) Diosmium – text and correspondence re publication of article, 1984-85 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Reactivity of Haloruthenocene(IV) Complexes – correspondence re publication of article, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of Stationary Electrode Pulse & Cyclic Voltammetry for Determination of… – text, figures, and correspondence re publication of article, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Interactions of the Ruthenium(III)-(II) couple with Malononitrile and Related Ligands – text and correspondence re publication of article, 1979-82 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Reexamination of the Co(NH3)6 Self-Exchange Rate – correspondence re publication of article and figures, 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Preparation and Properties of Mixed-Valence μ-Dinitrogen-bis(pentaammine) Complexes of Osmium & Ruthenium – correspondence re publication of article with text and figures, 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Observation of a Reversible Adsorbed Redox Couple Using, etc. – correspondence re publication of article, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Aquo chemistry of Monoarene complexes of Os(II) and Ru(II) – text and correspondence re publication of article, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Linkage Isomerization in Amide Complexes of Ruthenium Pentaammines – text, figures, and correspondence re publication of article, 1983-84 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Svatos, George, correspondence and notes, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Storm, Carl B., correspondence and note, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Matwiyoff, Nick, correspondence and notes, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Snellman (?), Jim, correspondence 1963 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Linck, Robert G., correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Barcelona – inorganic colors [transparencies] (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Office of Naval Research – research proposals and reports, 1955-64 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Triethyl Phospite as a Ligand on Ruthenium(II) – correspondence with co-author Douglas W. Franco and illustrations 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NSF grant proposals 1958-65 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Grant proposals 1962-72 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AEC grant proposal and reports, 1968-70 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NIH grant proposals 1963-65 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NSF correspondence, 1979-80 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NIH grant proposal 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NSF grant proposal 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Low Dielectric Solutions, notes (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - RC1++ Equil., notes (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Reactions, notes (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Free radicals – abnormal valences: notes and letter from William C. Bray to Charles D. Coryell, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Reprints by Taube (5) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Wang, Sabina – Christmas card with photographs, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous slides (film): four unidentified men, 1 book jacket, 1 set of test tubs with formulas above (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Idea Channel [not viewed for content], 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Henry Taube from Gunther Schweir [not viewed for content], 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Gmelin englisch NTSC-version [not viewed for content] (Box 9)
  - "XXI Bienal de Quimica" conferencia a cargo del Premio Nobel de Quimica 1983. 25 de Septembre de 1986 [not viewed for content], 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Large Glass slide of 2 men sitting on a couch; labeled "U. of C. Clinics Photo Dept." (Box 9)
  - "Taube" [not reviewed for content], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9)
  - unlabeled [not reviewed for content], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9)
  - 20th Anniversary ACS AWARD for Distinguished Service in the Advancement of Inorganic Chemistry Dr. Henry Taube 1967. Sign on side of base reads: ACS – St. Louis, Missouri – 1984. Plaque includes replica of the St. Louis Gateway Arch, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 9)
  - Map case
    - Oversize photo collages (Box OS)
  - RESTRICTED BOX:
    - Papers by students in Taube's classes: James S. Dwyer 1958; Larry Ellis 1966; A. B. Hoffman 1964; Harold Toshio Inatomi 1941; Carlos Andrade undated; R. G. Linck undated; Edward Deutsch 1964; Edward Weissberger 1964. (Box 10)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2007-004
  - Henry Taube letters to John P. Hunt [former student] 1950s-1970s (Box 1)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2007-104
  - Henry Taube letters to John P. Hunt [former student], 1950s-1970s
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2007-148
  - Autograph Requests 2003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - B (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bray, William (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Catalytica (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Record (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - C (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - D (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Datta, Shouman (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dinitrogen Chemistry - General (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - F (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Annual report 9/00-8/01 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Flory, Paul (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Former Associates (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Frank, Pat (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Freshman-Sophomore 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Freshman Sophomore Class (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Freshman-Sophomore Seminar-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gas Phase Basicities and Acidities (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Group (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - H (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hasegawa, Tai (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Herzberg, Agnes (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hush, Noel (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Institute of Molecular Sciences (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Interoffice Memorandums (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - J (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Japan Proposal - 8/98 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Japan Trip File (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - K (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - L (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - M (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Meier, Roland (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Nufert, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - O (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - P (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Past Postdoctoral Possibilities (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Pauling, Linus (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Periana, Roy (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Postdoctoral Inquiries (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Publications (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Referee Reports (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Refereeing Proposals (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Ross, John (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Awards John Ross (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - S (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - T (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Tables - Numerical Data (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Taube Memorial Responses (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Telephone Bills (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Tsuchida-HT's Proposed Trip to Japan (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - U (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - V (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - W (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Waymouth, Bob (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - X (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Y (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Z (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Research Agreement (Pin Yang, Andrew Yeh, Henry Taube, Zai Wei Li) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Inner-Sphere Cluster Formation … Working File (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Inner-Sphere Cluster Formation … Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Ghosh, Frank Manuscript (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Inner-Sphere Cluster Formation … Original Paper and Referee Reports (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nanjing Paper 2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Inner-Sphere Cluster Formation By … Poulopoulou, Taube, Nunes (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Frank (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Interactions of Hexacyano Ions … V. Poulopoulou, H. Taube (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Tmtacn, Tacn and Triammine Complexes of … Wang, Eberspacher, Hasegawa, Day, Ware (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Tmtacn, Tacn and Triammine Complexes of … R. Wang, T. Eberspacher, T. Hasegawa, V. Day, D. Ware (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Sano Paper (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Probe Paper (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - The Structure of [Ru)NH3)5H2O]Fe … Hasegawa, Poulopoulou, Taube (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - (Work File) Interactions of Hexacyano Ions - V.G. Poulopoulou and H. Taube (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Cooperative Litigation, Back - …" Frank, Ghosh, Hodgson, Taube (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Yang Paper (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Synthesis and Characterization of … McQueen, Nagao, Eberspacher, Li, Taube (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - McQueen (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Park, Sunghan (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Poulopoulou, Vassiliki (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Vania Research File (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Tai Hasegawa (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Grant Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Budget - Grants Correspondence with Ed (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Sponsored Projects/Grant Corres. - General (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - NIH 4/1/96-3/31/99 - Bio Significant Molecules … not funded (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - NIH No-Cost Extension (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Biochemically Significant Molecules As Ligands - NIH - 4/1/93-3/31/96 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NIH Biochemically Significant Moleculesas Ligands - 4/1/92 - 3/31/93 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NIH Biochemically Significant Molecules as Ligands 4/1/91 - 3/31/92 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Biochemically Significant Molecules as Ligands - NIH 4/1/88-3/31/91 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Biochemically Significant Molecules as Ligands - NIH 1984/1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Biochemically Significant Molecules as Ligands - NIH GM13638 5 yr. proposal 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Biochemically Significant Molecules as Ligands - NIH GM13638 5 yr. proposal 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Biochemically Significant Molecules as Ligands - NIH GM13638 5 yr. proposal 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NSF Final Report 8/31/01 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NSF Supplemental Report - 2001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - NSF 3/1/98-2/28/2001 Oxidation-Reduction Mechanisms (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - NSF-CHE9505279 - 2/1/94-1/31/98 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - NSF-CHE-9505379 Supplemental Proposal 9/1/96-2/28/97 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - NSF-CHE9120158 - 1/1/92-12/31/94 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Oxidation-Reduction Mechanisms NSF Period 12/1/88-11/30/91 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Oxidation Reduction Mechanisms NSF 12/1/85-11/30/88 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Oxidatiohn Reduction Mechanisms NSF 11/1/82-5/31/84 CHE 8211275 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - NSF Supplemental Grant AP. 7-12/90 Oxidation Reduction Mechanisms (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - NSF - "A Block Travel Grant Request For Travel to the XXV Inter. Conf. '88" (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Oxidation Reduction Mechanisms NSF Proposal 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - National Science Foundation "Oxidation Reduction Mechanisms" CHE76-09812 11/1/76 to 10/31/77 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - NIH "Biochemically Significant Moleculaes as Ligands" GM13638-13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ACS "Reactivity of Binuclear Complexes of the Ruthenoscene" (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Back-bonding Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Back-bonding Argonne Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Backbonding in Chemistry of Ru(III) and Os(II) Ventura (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Tech Talk B. Bond (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ATA Conference Edmonton Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Backbonding (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Backbonding, China 2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Canberra, February 1996 Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Catalytica 2e Changes (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Catalytica - Japan (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Catalytiuca, July '96 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Catalytica Induction Effects (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Chem 153 First Part Substitution 1984 (Transparencies) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - China Lecture (delivered by Zawei Li) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Dihydrogen Complexes of Osmium Ammines - Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Dihydrogen Complexes - Osaka 2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dihydrogen Complexes (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Electron Transfer-Advanced Course (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ET, Brookhaven - 2e changes Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Electron Transfers in Chem Reactions BNL Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Electron Transfer - Freiburg Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Electron Transfer Japan 2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Electron Transfer, General - Japan Transparencies (also misc.) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Electron Transfer - Hawaii (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Halpern, Jack - Symposium 1996 Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ET, 1e/2e Changes Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Friedman Lecture (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Intramolecular, e.t. - Miscellaneous (Transparencies) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - German Meeting - Traditional Coordination Chemistry (Box 7, Folder 32)